USA
Thank you very much!
Like, at first...
When I came to the venue today, I was
like, there's a different venue?
There's a chair?
After this, I thought that all the
publicity staff would sit here.
I was so excited.
But on the other hand, I promised
everyone that I would definitely come
back with the publicity staff this time.
I promised at the July live.
I made a promise with everyone so soon.
I think I can definitely make a big
hit.
I made a promise with everyone from
this July live.
I was happy.
I'll do my best.
Let's go!
Let's go, NINGNING!
Thank you for watching! Please
subscribe to our channel!
This program is brought to you by six
people who are active to promote
something to your liking.
I'll prove my excitement to the future!
Happy New Day!
My first video, 1 March 2017
CHAWANSHUI
Please subscribe to my channel!
Her concentration just now…
It's embarrassing, but thank you.
What's this?
The first day of the performance
Thank you for your cooperation.
Thank you for your cooperation, Nibe.
What do you want to eat?
I brought water.
I drank 4 bottles of water today.
What is it?
Thank you for watching. Please
subscribe to our channel.
I'm going to do my part.
I can't move.
Yeah, you can't move.
I'm Nibu.
Can you see me?
I'll do my best.
If you have something to say, please
say it.
You're in the frame.
Don't take your hands off.
I'll watch it after the live.
Please watch the live after the live.
Thank you for coming to see us.
Please look forward to the second part.
I'm sorry.
We'll do our best.
I'm going to do my best!
Let's go NIMBU!
Thank you for coming to the Super Funda
Tokyo event today.
I'm Daiki from Super Funda Tokyo.
I'm Suzumura Kane from Super Funda
Tokyo.
I'm Yone from Super Funda Tokyo.
I'm going to say good morning to you.
Mayu!
Kanamin! Julian! Futoka! Haruka! Aki!
Hiyori!
School announcement Smash success!
Z videos are added sometimes, please
watch them.
It is impossible!
Permitted to CD at
Hey, serious, give me credit.
You should give a feature of attitude,
but you don't have a great sense of
humor.
whoosh
If you can't do it, you can't
understand it, and the lines are weird.
Oh, I didn't know if I was there or
not.
We can't call the bad couple the R
AMCARE, feels like...
That instantหมlining, was it a good
choice to make entrance?
if only I had done it myself...
Well, of course, I've been doing it all
the time, and I'm glad that everyone
sent me a comment.
It was exciting and fun, but after all,
I'm really happy that I can do the live
show with the publicity staff in front
of me and see their faces directly.
I feel happy when I have eyes and they
smile at me.
I got a lot of excitement today.
And I thought it was really fun to have
a live show with the publicity staff.
It was a day when I could feel again
that live shows are good.
It was really a different place just
because there were customers or not,
even though it was the same place as
Z-Haneda.
When I had my debut live show in July,
I had a stage where the audience was
always there, and I did something that
was unique to live broadcasting.
This time, I felt that it was great to
have a live show where the audience was
there and it was 100 times more fun.
I was able to meet everyone and do a
live show together, and I came to see
them.
The lyrics are very good.
Even if we are apart, we can somehow
connect.
I'm afraid I'll forget something
important.
Even if we are apart, we can
communicate with everyone through live
broadcasts and live shows.
I'm happy to be able to convey my
feelings directly and see everyone's
smiles and do a live show in the same
space.
I was happy just to see everyone
smiling.
Thank you.
I've been looking forward to today
because I've been getting a lot of good
news since the rehearsal.
When I have an audience in front of me,
I can imagine it more and it's more fun.
I'm glad I was able to meet everyone
and laugh.
I realized again that what I thought
was normal until now was really amazing.
I really enjoyed being with everyone.
Today, everyone was in front of me and
they were excited with me.
They were clapping and making eye
contact with me.
I was really happy.
I was a little nervous, but I was able
to relax.
I was able to see the PR staff because
I wanted to make eye contact with them.
I was relieved.
I was able to take another step forward
and meet them.
I thought it was special that the PR
staff were there.
I was happy just to see their smiles.
Woo-hoo!
Good job!
I'm always doing it wrong.
Thank you!
Thank you for watching!
I think it would be nice if we could
make a sound.
I think it was the time when we were
the strongest.
It was fun.
Aki-chan, how was your first live with
SUDEMURI?
I was really happy that everyone was in
front of me and said hello.
I hope we can spend more happy time
together like this.
Thank you very much.
See you at 9th Shibuya.
See you there.
Next.
See you.
Thank you very much.
My mom was beaten.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for watching. Please
subscribe to my channel.
I really didn't aim for anything.
I'm going to do a VTR after this.
It's an old VTR, but I don't know why.
We are now making our first album,
which is a new album of Super Excited
Promotion Team.
We are recording various songs such as
cute songs, good songs, and super good
songs.
It's a very good song.
I want to give up soon.
What's the next song?
Ping pong!
Wait a minute!
Aki-chan!
No, no, no!
Wait a minute!
We are still doing a live broadcast!
Don't say that, Aki-chan!
You are a terrible senpai!
I was a little spoiled.
You are spoiled by being asleep.
No, I can't do that!
You can't do that, because you'll get
in trouble.
And here's another announcement!
We announced the release date of the
album, which will be released this
winter.
The release date is Wednesday, December
23rd.
And we can now have a homepage for this
album!
Wow!
This is amazing!
Everyone, please check out this album!
And we have one more announcement!
Please take a look at the VTR!
Please!
It's a rock version!
Please check out the VTR!
Ah! Oharu...
Hey~~~
Are we done already?
Oh, now?
Ah! Oharu, you nagger!
My manager is now calling me a nagger.
You gave
us extra silence to hear that.
lol
Yesterday I was in another place,
but right now I am the MC,
so I was like,
what?
Wait,
I was like, what was that?
I'm glad that everyone laughed and
clapped.
Thank you for making it interesting.
I'm sorry.
I don't need it.
Someone help me.
Thank you so much for today.
When I did the live show without
audience last time,
there was a stage here,
and I had to scroll here,
and here,
and go down.
I have a timeline.
I scrolled here.
Scroll.
I'll deliver the best excitement to
everyone!
Let's turn our frustration and
happiness into excitement!
Always look at me, my precious feelings
I wonder if there's only today
I can't stop anyone anymore
I can't afford to look down
I'm so excited
I don't care what happens
My heart is beating again
Why am I so excited?
I want you to tell me more
I can see you guys in front of me
I can see your faces
I can see the other members too
Thank you so much
I love the members and I love you guys
I want to pursue bigger goals with the
members
Let's make the strongest theory of
everyday life
Let's go! Tomorrow! Tomorrow! Tomorrow!
The strongest theory!
Hello! Hello! To the new me!
I don't care what people say
I'll attack fiercely!
Tomorrow! Tomorrow! Tomorrow!
The strongest theory!
Hello! Hello! To the infinite
possibilities!
Challenge everything you want to do
Prove the exciting future
Ah! Happy New Day!
Let's go! Tomorrow! Tomorrow! Tomorrow!
Together, Tomorrow! The strongest
sense!
Go! Go! Tomorrow!
Together, Tomorrow! The strongest
sense!
The strongest sense!
If it's everyday, it's growth
Everyday, right?
When you think everything has a meaning
It's time to do it
It's not a love of fate
Even if there's no dream
I'll do my best
Thank you so much for coming to see the
live
There were a lot of times I couldn't
meet you
Among them, there were quite a few
people who knew about Saki-sen for the
first time and fell in love with it
I was able to think that the period
when I couldn't meet you was not in vain
It's been a long time since I met you
I love you more
It was a really great day to see your
smiles
I'm looking forward to the day when I
can make a live with you again
I will continue to move forward
Thank you so much for today
We will keep moving forward no matter
what happens
Thank you so much for supporting us
even during the time we couldn't meet
you
We will continue to show you our best
We want to show you our best that we
are satisfied with the fact that we
couldn't meet you
I hope you will continue to support us
We really really love you, Sendai
Musician
Thank you so much
We are so happy that we could meet you
We will hold a live concert in December
We will continue to make memories as a
super Tokimeki-san band
I would be happy if you could continue
to support us
We will keep sending you Tokimeki on
SNS
Please check it out
Please continue to support us
Thank you so much
Today's live concert was the first live
concert in 8 months
We always do live streams and we don't
have many fans
We had a lot of fans until now
But I forgot how it feels
It's a better view than I imagined
I hope we can have more fans when the
situation gets better
I'm so happy
We are going to be a super Tokimeki-san
We will keep moving forward so please
support us
I had a lot of fun today
Thank you so much
Please sleep a lot
Good night
Julia-chan is here
We will meet you again at Line Cube
Shibuya
I hope you can come to see us if you
couldn't
There were a lot of things I wanted to
tell you when I couldn't meet you
show you
I want to deliver my feelings to you at
the Live at Line Cube Shibuya
I want to show you a better me
I want to show you that we are the best
when we are together
I will do my best at the live concert
Please wait for us
Thank you so much
THIS IS NO SPECIFIC MOUSE
A door cannot be opened 2- Shang Tsung
Transform to 4 kinds of sounds
Oh?
Sorry but ten ringing stones won't
serve as powerup attacks, either...
Correct.
Then, I'll be bringing it home to you.
Hello everyone!
Good evening!
I have a cute picture of myself!
I'm Aran!
This is the 19th Wednesday of this
month.
Where did you get 19th?
Isn't it Wednesday?
It's a time-honored day, so I thought
it was Wednesday.
It's a birthday of my friend.
It's not the 19th.
19th is...
It's the 19th, isn't it?
No, it's not.
The 21st is the day of the sale.
The 19th is the day of the sale.
It's from 19 o'clock.
I see.
I said 19th.
By the way, Haru's dad is Hiyomi.
But he's a big rival to Kanamin.
I'm a big rival to Kanamin.
But I'm a junior high school student.
I'm a junior high school student.
Thank you for your advice.
Let's move on to the next one.
It's the one that they are competing
against each other.
I got a star.
It's the one that they are competing
against each other.
I might lose this one.
I think I'll get 152.
Kanamin is 21 years old.
How old is she?
She's not young anymore.
She's so mature.
What's this?
What's this lip?
She's smiling.
I want to kiss her.
That's good.
I'll kiss her big eyes.
Haru is going to lose.
I'm going to lose.
She's looking at me.
147.
What's this, An?
An, when did you start making this
face?
I miss the old An.
The new An is also amazing.
She was looking at me 2 years ago.
I think she's going to be a fan of An.
She's a fan.
What's this?
An is so cute.
I'll skip one.
Don't skip it.
Thank you for watching. Please
subscribe to our channel.
I'm cute.
I'm cute when I'm in a good mood.
I'm in a good mood.
What's your number?
It's 137.
It's cute.
It looks like a hairband.
I think it'll be fun if everyone does
it.
It's cute.
It's a fluffy feeling.
It's like a forest girl.
It looks good on you.
It's cute.
You have a good mouth.
I'm embarrassed.
Can I say it?
Do you think so?
I don't understand.
It's getting hot.
It's funny.
Let's move on to the next.
It's cute.
It's like a different world.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Wow!
We heard a lot.
Why do you like this pop style?
It's like America.
It's like a pop style with a little bit
of American style.
Or alien style.
Alien?
Alien hair looks good on you.
I think it would be good to wear it in
America.
Yes, it's called American girl.
I've heard that a lot.
Everyone is a little mature.
It's a Japanese style.
It's a Japanese style, but it's like
Aki-chan.
It's like American girl.
And Aki-chan is wearing a different
jacket than this.
It's a ribbon.
There are a lot of ribbons.
It looks good on both of us.
It's cute.
Please subscribe to our channel.
I'm in my first year of high school.
I look good in sporty clothes.
I look good in anything.
You look like a foreigner.
I look like a junior.
I can go to Korea.
I can go to France.
I have a face that goes beyond my
hometown.
I have a face.
Do you want to skip this?
I skip this.
I'm sad.
This is the first question.
What kind of face do you have?
Why?
I'm laughing.
I have a sexy face.
I like the costume at this time.
I've never seen it before.
I'm chic.
I have a big lip on my lips.
I have a good lip.
It's true.
It's plump.
We shot a cool video like this.
What's next?
We came to Gumi.
Oh!
We came here.
Thank you.
140.
148.
Actually, we are going to do a
calculation ceremony.
We are going to show you how cute we
are.
Is it okay?
Yes.
Everyone, let's start the calculation
ceremony.
Jessie's speedy calculations
I got the answer.
This picture is of a person in Sakai.
Is it the opposite?
The opposite?
Which one is the opposite?
This one.
This is the person in Sakai.
I want it.
This is the picture of Ryuki in the
first seat.
Ryuki is in the first seat.
This is not right.
For example, if I say that I want to
eat apple,
she will say, yes.
If I do that, she will say, no.
Please subscribe to our channel.
I can see the red carpet everywhere.
Red carpet.
I can see it.
Please subscribe to our channel.
I'm going to ride a red carpet.
You're going to ride it all at once.
Thank you very much.
I want number 748.
What kind of video is this?
I'm going to ride a red carpet.
I see.
You look like a woman.
No.164
Please look at this.
I'm jealous of her face.
I'm jealous of Sakai's face.
Oharu is cute, too.
I'm jealous of her.
I can see it.
Oharu is jealous.
She loves Kitoka and Hiyorin so much.
She loves them so much.
The moment I saw this, the staff was
also very surprised.
It was Sakai-san who made such an
expression.
So, live broadcast will be on air from
Wednesday, 21st.
Please check it out.
Please experience it.
I'm angry.
Bye bye!
I've talked a lot, and my shadow has
grown longer
I wonder if I want to go home soon
I love you
I was able to say, I'll do my best,
I'll do my best
Stay by my side a little longer
I love you, I love you
I'm happy just being like this
The bench in the water
It never changes
When the lights in the city were on
The scent of love passed by
The bench is still waiting for someone
I remember the day I spent with you
Even if I try drinking the juice I
liked
It seems a little too much for one
person
Even now, I have a lot of fun memories
Glittering in the sky
I tried to stretch out my hands as much
as I could
I tried my best, but
I'm sure I can't reach you anymore
I love you, I miss you
Every time I think of you like this
The back of my chest tightens
The bench in the water
It's still waiting
It never changes
I'm waiting for someone
You're not coming back here anymore,
are you?
The only thing I could say was,
Stay by my side a little bit more
I love you. I love you.
Hey, I'll never ever forget
Under the sky that has opened up
I love you. I love you.
I'm happy just to be with you.
This moment is happiness.
The rainbow-colored bench
will never change.
Benji!
I'll paint your world!
Thank you for watching!